riflepaperco.com 2019-02-01

# Help | RIFLE PAPER Co.

#### 407-622-7679

#### [help@riflepaperco.com](mailto:help@riflepaperco.com)

#### [Faq](https://riflepaperco.com/faq/)

Our highest priority is to provide quality products and excellent personal service to our valued customers. We try to be easily accessible, addressing all requests and concerns as efficiently as we can. We are looking to build life-long relationships with our customers, and hope that you will be one of them. Please let us know if there is anything we can do to improve our service.  

## Returns & Exchanges

  1. ### Make Sure Your Order Qualifies

Pillows, personalized orders, and made-to-order frames are not eligible for returns.

To learn more or to authorize a return for rugs, wallpaper, or fabric please contact help@riflepaperco.com.

Orders may be returned so long as:

    * The order is new, unused/unworn, and in the original packaging
    * The order is returned within 15 days of receipt
    * The order was not purchased on final sale
  2. ### Return Your Order & Packing Slip

With the exception of rugs and wallpaper, please send your order and its original packing slip, to:

RIFLE PAPER CO.  
Attn: Returns  
140 Atlantic Drive  
Maitland, FL 32751 USA

Any order returned to the wrong address (i.e. the address not provided in the return form) will incur a rerouting fee subtracted from the refund.

If you are looking to make an exchange for an item of equal or lesser value, please note which item(s) you would like to receive on your original packing slip.

Please keep the tracking number and any other relevant shipping information in the unlikely event we do not receive your return shipment.

  3. ### Await Credit

Once a qualified return is received we will process your refund as soon as possible. The charges placed on your card will be credited to you, excluding non-refundable shipping costs. Rugs are subject to a restocking fee.

Please note refunds may take up to ten (10) business days to show on your account due to varying processing times between payment providers. If for any reason you do not receive the credited amount within that time frame, please feel free to [contact us](https://riflepaperco.com/contact/).

## Shipping / Payment

Shipping & Fulfillment

Rifle Paper Co. currently ships all orders with either FedEx or USPS from our shipping and fulfillment warehouse in Maitland, FL  with the exception of a few items. Rugs and pillows will ship from Dallas, TX and wallpaper will ship from Hudson, WI.

International Shipping

We currently offer FedEx options for international orders. Rifle Paper Co. is not responsible for any customs fees or duties incurred on international shipments as these are the responsibility of the purchaser. We strongly recommend using International First or Priority methods if you need your package to arrive in a time sensitive manner. Please note, however, even with these shipping methods, transit times may vary due to customs delays. International Standard, while an affordable method, may vary in transit time and reliability depending on your own country's postal system.

At this time, we are only able to ship rugs and pillows to the United States, US Territories, and Canada.

Rug Shipping & Restocking Fees

Each rug in your order ship individually and incur its own shipping fee. Should you wish to return your rug, an equal restocking fee will apply. Please note, return shipping costs will be the responsibility of the customer.

Domestic shipping and restocking fees are:

Over $900 | $75  
---|---  
$250–$900 | $35  
$75–$250 | $15  
Up to $75 | $10  
  
Signature required upon delivery for all rug orders excluding PO Boxes and APO/FPO. At this time, we are only able to ship rugs and pillows to the United States, US Territories, and Canada.

Personalized Order Processing

Personalized orders typically take about 2–3 weeks to process and ship. If your order is time sensitive please [contact us](https://riflepaperco.com/contact/) before placing your order. If you order additional store products they will be shipped at the same time as the personalized goods. Please see the product descriptions for more information.

Lost Packages

If you have a package that was marked as delivered but you have not yet received it, we ask you take the following steps:

  * Check with your neighbors or front office (if applicable) to see if the package was left there
  * Reach out to your local post office or FedEx facility.
  * Contact our team at help@riflepaperco.com and include your order number.

We kindly ask that you report your lost or stolen shipment within 10 days of the marked delivery date. If an order is lost after being shipped to a third party mail forwarding facility, we are unable to assume responsibility of the package once it is marked as delivered. Once an international shipment has been marked as ‘delivered,’ we are no longer responsible for the particular package.

_Please note, Rifle Paper Co. is not responsible for refunding or reshipping lost orders due to an incorrect address at checkout._

## Terms / Conditions

Content Usage

Please [contact us](https://riflepaperco.com/contact/ "Contact") should you wish to use any of our content or make reference to Rifle Paper Co. publicly. Along with seeking our permission we ask that you provide credit for any content you intend to re-use, and hyperlink it to <https://riflepaperco.com/> if used online. Whenever possible, we are happy to provide high resolution photographs and answer any questions you may have at that time.

_We reserve the right to request that any third-party remove our content or other copyrighted materials at any time for any reason._

Copyright & Trademarks

_Rifle Paper Co._  and _riflepaperco.com_ are properties of Rifle, Inc. In addition, any photos, designs, graphics, text or other content are protected by worldwide copyright and other intellectual property laws, treaties and protections. You may not reproduce, publish, distribute, transmit, transfer, sell or modify any portion of this site without express written permission from Rifle, Inc.

_All third party names, trademarks and copyrights are properties of their respective owners._

Community Guidelines

We reserve the right to block, delete, or otherwise restrict comments and posts from our social media channels which contain personal attacks, hateful or divisive speech, profanity – or those which promote a personal, political, or other unrelated business or agenda. We hope this will promote an atmosphere where our friends, customers, and fans can engage in productive and positive conversation.

## Privacy / Security

Information Gathering

_We only collect the personal information you choose to provide_. When you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter some of your personal information is required. You may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may visit our site anonymously by declining to engage in any of these interactions.

Information Usage

The information you provide us may be used in any of the following ways:

  1. Personalize your experience

  2. Improve our website

  3. Process a transaction

  4. Provide you with order status

  5. Send Rifle Paper Co. promotional messages.

_Note: You may unsubscribe from our promotional messages by following the unsubscribe instructions located at the bottom of each message._

The information you submit to us, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or requested service.

Information Protection

_All data submitted is transmitted via https (TLSv1.2)._ Any data submitted in relation to a purchase is also encrypted before being sent to our payment gateway provider for authorization. We employ a variety of measures to protect your personal information when it is submitted to our site. The payment gateway provider is required by law to keep this information confidential. We do not store any financial information (credit cards, social security numbers, etc.) on our servers. The personal information we do store on our servers (name, address, email, phone number, etc.) is protected by standard industry-wide security measures. Compromising the security measures employed by us or by our payment gateway provider is punishable by law.

Fraud Prevention

Internet fraud is a serious matter. We encourage you to be cautious about submitting your financial information online and to vet any organization which purports to protect your information. If you feel that you have been the victim of fraudulent purchase activity through our store, please contact your bank (or related financial institution) immediately. Unless instructed not to by your financial institution, [contact us](https://riflepaperco.com/contact/) next. If the questionable transaction is “pending” there is a chance we can cancel it before any money has been exchanged. If the payment has been processed, please [contact us](https://riflepaperco.com/contact/) so that we can put a hold on it before it gets shipped. We will do everything in our power to prevent the processing of fraudulent orders, inclusive to contacting you by phone or email to verify your payment and shipping information.

Cookies

We use cookies to help us remember you, process items in your shopping cart and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can provide a better site experience. [Learn more about cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie).

Third Parties

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential and so long as they agree to comply with our policies. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property or safety. Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses, but is refreshed every 28 days.

Third Party Links

At our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We claim no responsibility or liability for the content and / or activities of these third parties, though we welcome any feedback about them – [contact us](https://riflepaperco.com/contact/ "Contact").

COPPA Compliance

In compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to individuals who are at least 13 years or older.

GDPR Compliance

In compliance with the requirements of GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation), we allow customers to:

  * Manage their personal data
  * Request we cease processing their personal data
  * Request access to any of their personal data for whatever use they see fit
  * Request we remove their personal data entirely

Customers and site visitors interested in any of the above should email [help@riflepaperco.com](mailto:help@riflepaperco.com) and we will be happy to assist.

Privacy Policy

This online privacy policy applies to information collected through our website and not information collected offline. By using our site, you consent to our Terms & Conditions and Privacy & Security policies. By placing an order through our site you consent to our Customer Service policies.

_We reserve the right to change these policies at anytime.  Please [contact us](https://riflepaperco.com/contact/) if you have any questions about the above information._
